javaads.com 2017-02-20

# Beach.com Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy — Beach.com

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices of beach.com located at http://www.beach.com (the "Site").

 **How We Collect and Use Information**  
If you choose to receive communication from beach.com, we will ask you to provide us with your name and email address. If you choose to register using Facebook Connect, we will automatically receive and retain basic account registration data you previously provided to Facebook, including name, email address, Facebook user ID and Facebook page URL.

We will use your email address to send you one or more invitations or reminders to register for, test or use the Service or visit the Site. From time to time, we may also send you other transactional or promotional email related to the Service. Email messages we send you may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the emails, including whether the email was opened and what links (if any) were clicked. If you would rather not receive emails from us at any time, simply click on the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email message. We fully comply with the requirements of the U.S. CAN-SPAM Act.

Any time you visit the Site, our servers may automatically gather non-PII from your browser (such as your IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks). We do not share this information externally.

 **Age Restrictions**  
We do not target our Site or Service to children under the age of 13, and in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, any information we may receive from users we believe to be under the age of 13 will be purged from our database. If you are under age 13, do not use the Site or register for the Service.

 **Geographic Restrictions**  
Users may not access the Site, register for or use the Service if prohibited by law in their country of residence.

 **Disclosure of Your Information to Third Parties**  
We may share your PII with service providers that may be associated with us to perform functions on our behalf. Your information will be treated as private and confidential by such service providers and not used for any other purpose than we authorize.

You acknowledge and agree that we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law, at the request of a third party, or if we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is reasonable to comply with the law, requests or orders from law enforcement, or any legal process; protect or defend our rights or property; or protect someone's health or safety.

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets and, depending on the transaction, your PII may be one of the transferred assets. In the event that we are acquired by another company, your PII may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party. If this occurs, you will be notified if there are any material changes to the way your PII is collected or used.

We will only share your information with third parties in the ways defined in this privacy statement.

 **Security**  
We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information stored in our database. We will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, but given that no information transmitted over the Internet can be guaranteed 100% secure, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and hence accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.

 **Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the Site, or your dealings with the Service, you can contact us at [info@beach.com](mailto:info@beach.com)

 **Acceptance of Privacy Statement**  
Your use of the Site, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this privacy statement. BY USING THE SITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement page and any other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by other means, such as email, at our discretion.

Your continued use of any portion of the Site following posting of the updated privacy statement will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

Effective Date

 _This privacy statement was last revised on October 26, 2010._
